For the non-special utility, we need to know that these people might get to know what they're going to do.
See you again now.
So, I think we'll have the...
Yeah.
Isn't it more or less than I get to?
Let's pray.
Fair enough, I'll thank you so much, Lord, that we can get a day to see.
But, Father, I ask you to be at the...
Our leaders as they make decisions tonight,
that you can just tell them to make wise and correct decisions.
Father, I pray that you can be at all our employees and families as a work for the city,
just to take you to watch over the city.
I'll just pray these things across the day.
Amen.
I'll pledge allegiance to this lab,
and be united to the states of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, I'm very good in the visible liberty and justice problem.
For four bulletin get lit, that's good in the first bullet care system.
For five, seven, ten, ten, ten.
For that we can get to the east blue, I don't see.
So, second.
Four men.
Four, five.
Two men.
Five, five.
Five.
the field of services for the 23 alley, land, and acquisition services.
Not that C, 21, 24, without 3 or $5,000.
This is the part of the bond project that we previously had got.
This is one of the projects that we set out to do.
So we have this section of Peter 23 that goes from,
give it a full of our all-white support that we don't request.
It is then going on now.
So it's an alley that we really can access.
So we have a real goal here to walk in there.
Now we have a little track machine that will go in and out.
We really have some way to get in and out.
You can have seated drawings up there.
So what we would like to do.
This is something that we wanted to do for a long, long time.
So whenever we have a storm, we have it.
So when I say Peter, it's like a main.
It's like a main.
It's like a main line.
It starts out to the North West.
So we come here to become a substation.
And if he's off of there, it's time to do those quests.
So whenever we have an alley, we send the guys.
And after he did a look at the lecture, you know,
that if we had a tornado, we had a lot of strikes.
Something the line is only on the ground before he decides to do something.
I'm going to call her.
So we can actually do that.
I'm going to try to do this with the guys.
I think that's awesome.
So with this work order, you know, me, we hire a company that's working as a poor
organization.
I'm saying something.
It's a problem.
So we actually work doing why are even, you have a lot of alley.
So we can drive trust.
you have enough work to get it and how to make it work.
But it's something that should have been done a long time ago.
So you're going to go from get rich all the way to for that, you know, but there's about
66 parcels that are on the way to work with.
And this is something that's active in the house.
You know, there's a lot of letters that we send.
There's a lot of discussion with one more, like what they're doing, you know, this is
something like how I think you're looking through these things that you've been
in the year.
So you just need to go into the house, you have the things that you're going from.
So you need to go into, you know, from get rich.
To get rich, so you don't have enough letters, and you go from about to get it.
Down in the house between age and age and age.
Well, if you're an age, then you're an age.
And then you're an age.
And then it's seven.
So that the terms that goes about.
And if you've noticed when you come in from the administration, on the third or
third class, we could make a lot of holes there.
We kind of work back on that direction.
But that's where we had to stop that because when we came in early trucks and they.
Well, we'll, you know, exactly as well.
It's not a lot.
I mean, they will work within the movement.
But there's not a lot of, you know, I know, because the gastroenterology has been working
to be able to get to the house now.
So there's a few meters.
And they're in the back of the show.
Like they usually do.
We also have a sewer.
A lot of that.
So we can actually get our trucks and they're in the back of the sewer.
So we have a stoppage and everything.
I mean, I'll all need to leave.
So for each of the, each of the, each other's good.
Is there something to do?
We have to leave.
And I've been working for 18 to the positive, obviously.
18 to the negative.
They're going to work with us.
That helps with the other.
So it kind of works with us.
It works.
It working.
But it works.
It works.
That works.
OK.
You can all play, and
we're moving on to the director's table.
Let's trust the Indian out.
We'll try to look within it.
So, let's go.
Okay.
Please get to work.
I'll go.
Bye.
We'll start.